I'm on a journey out to see the world.
While I'm on my own, I've
yet to reach the end.
So won't you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea.
For that treasure known
by everybody as one piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon, the rain
will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the
anchor, now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm the storm
that you have built within.
Come and have my board at number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up,
we set self cause we can't.
Thresh enough, stand tall and
take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me wanna see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second,
it's not the truth.
That's the story most will believe.
Not me, come and see.
I am on a journey out to sea.
The world done on my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done?
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can.
Yes, we can!
Wha...
What is this?
How'd this happen? Hey!
Hey, where is everybody?
Who did this to Zoe?
I'll make whoever's behind this pain.
Don't tell me it was those depraved,
straw-hot virus behind all this destruction.
What the hell did they do to my home?
This fortress was a living space
once inhabited by our ancestors.
Since ancient times,
Zunesha has carried the entire
history of the Mink tribe on its back.
One of our most cherished traditions
has been passed down for generations.
The trading of clothes with an
outsider is a symbol of friendship.
Wow, how gorgeous!
Must belong to someone important, huh?
Indeed so.
It's a national treasure.
And it's for me?
Of course.
We insist that you have it.
Crush!
Garchu-chu!
Mademoiselle, Crush.
Why, Crush?
How about you? Crush.
Crush, sir?
Tristan!
Crush!
Crush! Crush!
You two, you sure like our greeting, huh?
Oh!
Crush!
What a miraculous magic word!
Even though I don't know what it means!
Sanji here!
We want to do a round of Crush
with our savior! Piss off!
It's ladies only!
Hello there, Sanji!
Crush!
Viva l 'amintimusia!
A goddess?
No!
Mommy!
Don't you!
Maybe not!
Where's Momo?
He's locked himself away in his room.
He was suffering from anxiety.
Besides, it's better if he's incognito.
That's a good point.
While we're at it, we should avoid
the word samurai while we're here.
Well, if it were up to me, I'd
hand the brat over to the minx.
And ditch this dumb
island already. Shut up!
What's the update on the medicine, Caesar?
Naturally, I met the
quota since I'm a genius.
Stop slacking!
There's still a great deal
of people in need of help.
Make more.
I think we have more than enough, though.
Dr.
Caesar, I've come to pick up the medicine.
You must have me mixed
up with someone else.
I'm Cedar the pharmacist. Here.
Damn, why do I have to make
this crap to help people?
Thank you, Tia. Dr. Caesar.
It's Cedar!
Man, I'm supposed to be Caesar the genius
mad scientist, not the charity worker.
Oh, almost forgot. Call me Cedar!
Heya, Baron Corpse.
Some fans are waiting outside.
I know they only want me for my bones.
Let's not entertain that.
Hey, Peckholms, good to see you, Conney.
It's been a while. Welcome back.
I'm so happy to see you're all okay.
Dad, Mom, my friends and
family, you're all alive.
It's been way too long.
Hey, Peckholms, this
brings back good memories.
It's so wonderful to have
you, Conney, back home.
Got you.
You idiot!
How can you be so happy when
you're covered in cuts and bruises?
My heart nearly stopped when I saw the
state that the city was in! Ease up!
That hurts, Pickles!
It's all thanks to the Straw Hat
Pirates that were still alive.
If it weren't for their
compassion and quick action,
I'm afraid to think of what
would have happened to us.
I'm so glad.
Thank you for hanging in there for me.
Come on, stop crying!
Dammit, I will never forgive.
Junk of the Beast Pirates
for as long as I live!
How dare he terrorize my innocent old lad?
That's them, they're
from the Big Mom Pirates.
They must have tailed us.
That's Peckham's down there!
He finally came back.
That kid was a troublemaker growing up.
So he's a mint?
Guess that makes sense, actually.
They must have overheard
where we were heading.
They're coming for me!
Whatever you do, please don't
hand me over, pretty please.
Don't forget that you are our trump
card for dealing with Doflamingo.
Now that Luffy and the others have beaten
him, we don't have a use for you anymore.
Now how could you say that to me?
We're bros, aren't we?
When did we become bros?
So, what the hell did you do to
piss off Big Mom? Spit it out.
I know you're hiding something from us.
Look, just hear me out, okay?
I accepted a grant for
research from Big Mom,
and I haven't quite gotten
anywhere with it yet,
so I lied and pocketed all the money.
Can you blame me?
Doe Flamingo had my back at the time,
so I may have gotten a bit carried away.
Sounds like you earned this.
If they're just looking for
Caesar, that's no big deal.
Once I get there,
I'm gonna kick your ass, and then
I'll make Fishman Island my territory!
Although that may not be the case,
Luffy did pick a fight with Big Mom.
We busted up their ship pretty good, too.
Listen, Blackleg, how about we work
together and take out the goons?
Nami, stay here with everyone.
And Brooke, you come with me. Understood.
Are you still considering my
brilliant assassination proposition?
I'm not looking for
suggestions from dumbasses.
AHHHHH!
Alright you guys, what
exactly do you want?
The people of this land have had their
fair share of suffering recently.
I'd rather not add to
their list of traumas.
Can we try to talk things over first?
I just wanted to say thank you so much!
Enough already.
I never expected to come back home and
see it completely devastated like this.
Get out!
But you and your crew may
selflessly save my people.
You're the reason they're alive!
How could I ever repay you?
Mama gave two orders.
First was to capture Caesar, but this
second one won't be too pleasant.
It might even mean the end of
the road for the Straw Hat crew.
That's ominous.
So I'm calling it!
The mission isn't failure.
Just hand over Caesar!
I'll explain to mama that we let the
Stryhats get away this time, okay?
You gotta choke those feelings down,
kid, if you knows what's good for you.
Shut the hell up, new guy!
I'm gonna take the fall for it!
You don't understand the position I'm in.
I can't do anything to the people who
saved the lives of my friends and family.
Yellow-bellied rat.
Oh, damn you.
Why'd he shoot him? They're allies.
What a monster.
Was that real? Can't be.
He don't look it, but he's
got quite the rap sheet.
Unfortunately, he decided to act on his
stupid feelings, and now he's gone soft.
Yeah, he ain't no good to me now.
I'll finish the job.
Look alive, boys.
Do your stuff.
Go!
No!
What's going on?
You're outnumbered.
You might as well surrender.
Where did they come from?
His gut?
How messed up is that? Indeed.
I saw those men in his hand.
But I thought I imagined it.
That's on account of
the castle castle fruit.
Your captain and I,
we're both considered to be part
of the same generation of pirates.
This guy knows me.
Don't you, pal?
When Luffy clocked that
celestial dragon back at Sabaody,
you were there with the rest
of the worst generation, huh?
But we ain't trying to make a scene here.
Let's keep this thing quiet.
That's better for everybody.
If any of the minks show up, then it's a
pretty good bet they'll take your side.
And believe you me, those
cats really know how to scrap.
Vino!
Hey, cut that out! Let us go!
Nami! Chopper!
Sorry, guys.
We were getting really curious.
And we thought there
were only two of them.
Hey, Caesar!
You can come out now!
Or we can fill you full
of holes with these
sea prism stone bullets
in about three seconds.
Three...
Two...
Light him up!
Wait, here I come! Don't shoot!
Don't point those at me!
Actually, it occurs to me we
ain't got no sea prism stone ammo.
How dare you?
What we do have is a spear
that'll work the same way.
I think we ought to continue this
conversation inside my castle.
That's an order.
I ain't got all day.
Great.
This bastard's calling all the shots.
So we were forced to enter.
THE END
Sorry to make you wait
Is anybody hungry?
Don't be shy.
Not interested.
Oh come on, lighten up.
Glass of wine.
I said no.
Just get to the point already.
This is it.
I'm going to die in this gangster's gut.
I just know it.
It sure wouldn't kill
you to relax a little.
About a week ago, you and I took
a couple of shots at each other.
However, the situation's evolved.
I've been asked to make sure
that this invitation reaches you.
Your presence is requested
at Mama's Tea Party.
You're kidding me.
Do I look like the kind of guy
who'd want to sip tea with Big Mom?
It's not just a tea party.
There's a wedding. Count me out.
The groom-to-be is the
third son of the Vinsmokes.
Sanji.
Wait, what?
And the lucky dame is the 35th daughter
of the Charlotte family, Puddin.
What?
So there's a wedding?
And Sanji's the groom-to-be?
You can keep this.
Why now of all times?
Hell should I know what
kind of deal you folks made.
Ya punk?
Trying to burn my castle down?
Hey, Sanji, what gives?
Are you really gonna get married?
who's bright idea was this and why you're
the vinsmoke here how
am i supposed to know
that although in your
case i'd say the apple
must have fallen pretty far from the tree
sanji's a vinsmoke that
chills me to the bone
which is quite the
predicament to find yourself
in in my case there
must be some mistake hey
top off my wine sir what
do we know about sanji
Yeah, have you heard of it, Sanji?
It says right here the book was
originally published in the North Blue
It was.
I was born in the North Blue Territory.
I'm certain I must have told you
guys that Oh, that's news to me.
Huh, I always thought you
were born in the East.
I grew up there.
Eh, what's the difference?
I remember feeling strange
when he told us that.
We met him in the East Blue, but
he was born in the North Blue.
It's all coming back to me now? What?
Are you sure, Nami?
Because if that's true,
then this is a big deal.
If you wanted to travel from
the North Blue to the East Blue,
then you'd have to cross
the Red Line. Exactly.
Is that super hard to do? Yes.
It's not just any ordinary old sea voyage.
It's a feat.
And Sanji, he was just a child.
You do realize, Charlotte happens
to be the surname of Big Mom, right?
He's marrying the child of the most
ruthless woman in the new world!
You're right!
That means he's joining
an emperor's family!
It's far worse than that!
If she has a member of your
crew as her son-in-law,
then the whole lot of you
will become her underlings!
Don't jump to conclusions. Huh?
Tea party, my ass.
You can't make me do it.
This is insane.
They want me to marry a
girl I don't even know,
and I have to find out by getting
an invite to my own wedding.
You're crazy if you think I'm gonna let
the Straw Hats become your playthings!
That'll never work—our captain
doesn't take orders from anybody!
Not
Luffy, because he's gonna
be king of the pirates.
pirates
Are we done here or what?
If you want Caesar, he's all yours I think
you might have the wrong idea, my friend.
The invitation was just
a matter of formality.
I wasn't asking whether you would accept.
Look around you, you're inside
my body, you're trapped.
I'm handing you over to mama
like lambs to the slaughter!
and there ain't nothing you
saps can do about it. What?
You probably haven't noticed
it, but I'm already on my way.
I don't feel it's moving at all.
That woman will kill me for sure.
Let me out of here.
Damn you.
If you want to rumble, we can do that.
Ganji, no!
This is my turn.
I control everything here.
I could clobber you with
anything in this room.
Help me!
The door's swollen high! Nami, no!
That's enough.
I said stop, dirtbag!
Are you okay, Nami? Yeah.
That scared me.
Even if I didn't smack your pals around,
you couldn't excuse yourself
from Mama's deep arty anyhow.
Because there's a little something
everybody in the new world knows.
Right.
Bittersweets and empty seats.
Those are two things
Mama won't allow, Lili.
Whenever someone tells her no, Lili.
Well, let's just say it
ain't a pretty picture.
And there's a lot of tears involved.
So choose carefully, Lili.
Nyololololo.
A tea party invite from Mama.
Is something you just don't turn down.
It's a requirement.
Or better yet, it's the law, Lili.
Everybody has to go.
Even the devil himself won't refuse Mama.
Capisce?
Of course, you can always no-show,
Lili, but, uh, you would regret that.
Better listen closely, Lili.
New Where the hell did you get that info?
Where do you think?
Don't you know who we answer to?
The four emperors are the toughest
contenders around, so they run the new world.
And of course, one of
them is Big Mom herself.
But she always gets her way.
If she decides a guy's dead, then
pow, he's sleeping with the fishes.
She doesn't bluff.
So every word out of that mug
of yours could be life or death.
If you intend to survive, and you
don't want to end up Mama's lapdog,
I'd play along for the time being.
Sanji?
Are you alright?
What did that man say to you just now?
Nyolu?
If you tell us we can help you, no
matter how bad she is, we can beat her!
Quiet already!
Let me borrow a pen and some paper.
Aw, is that a cute note to Straw Hat?
Take this.
It's for the crew.
Sanji, wait—you can't.
Nami, Chopper,
Brook—I want you all to know this.
I never meant to hide anything
from my friends. Okay.
That's a
part of my past.
I didn't think I'd ever
have to deal with again.
But it
caught up to me, and I have to
settle this once and for all.
You mean
you're doing this all by yourself?
You don't need to do.
I feel a powerful presence outside—probably
someone from the Mink Tribe!
the mink tribe Huh?
Are you ready?
Uh, for what?
Good luck, you three.
Threw me, too!
Oh, crap!
You helped his bunnies get away!
You little bastard!
All right, everybody, stay put.
Curses, why me?
Listen closely.
I know this scumbag's important to you.
So don't make me blow
his genius brains out.
You are going to pay for this someday.
That's what I thought.
You guys aren't allowed
to kill me. Are you?
With all this talk about the wedding.
I put two and two together.
On my poster.
In big bold letters.
It says only alive!
If you kill me, then somebody is
going to be really pissed off.
And let me guess, they said to treat me
respectfully with no handcuffs, right?
The one who got those words on my
poster and the one who set this wedding?
I bet they're the same person!
Quirk, we gotta go capture the other two.
Did I tell you to move?
Stay put for my sake!
As I was saying, you know exactly
who's got my back, don't you?
And I need to sort things
out with that person,
which means I am coming along with you,
so don't you dare lay
a finger on my friends!
Nobody is moving a
muscle, hurt, but father
be cool, would you?
There's a monster right
outside the castle—master
cat viper, it's you!
We didn't realize you were awake.
The hell is he a giant cat?
What does he want?
Hey, you gotta—what's going on here?
Care to
explain to me why I just found Peck
arms in a pool of his own blood?
You got it all wrong, my friend!
He's my Gourmet!
Gourmet,
you heard me from the
same pirate group—we got
roughed up by a few of the
stragglers from Jack's crew.
See?
No, he's lying!
Don't listen to this jerk!
Face what would I want
to shoot my own guy for?
Please come out, Sanji!
Why are you doing this?
I don't know why we can't join you.
Let's just wait for everyone
else—we're much stronger!
else we're much stronger
together, aren't we?
It's my problem to solve.
I'll be back soon.
So give everybody my best, okay?
Castle Tank, go!
Don't leave us
Nami! Chopper!
I'll try to catch him I
fear it's no use, Wanda.
But I don't understand.
I'm afraid he's made up his mind.
There's nothing we can do now.
Thank you.